politics4all.com 2009-11-23

# Privacy Policy | Politics4All - Real World Politics Daily

Politics4All takes your right to privacy seriously, and wants you to feel comfortable with using our site, contributing content, and interacting with other members. This privacy policy deals with personally-identifiable information (referred to as "information" below) that may be collected by this site. This policy does not apply to other entities that are not owned or controlled by Politics4All, nor does it apply to persons that are not employees or agents of Politics4All. Please take time to read our Terms of Use. 

By using Politics4All, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information as outlined in this Privacy Policy. 

### Information Collected

We only collect personal information that is relevant to the purpose of our Website, which is to enable users to discover and share information with one another. We do not process this information in a way that is incompatible with this objective. We collect the following types of information from our users: registration, personal information, location, photos, traffic data, IP address, cookie information, and any other information that allows us to provide you with a customized and efficient experience. 

### Use of Information

Information may be used to customize and improve your user experience on this site. Efforts will be made to prevent your information being made available to third parties unless (i) provided for otherwise in this Privacy Policy; (ii) your consent is obtained, such as when you choose to opt-in or opt-out for the sharing of information; (iii) a service provided on our site requires interaction with a third party, or is provided by a third party, such as an application service provider; (iv) pursuant to legal action or law enforcement; (v) it is found that your use of this site violates the site’s policy, terms of use, or other usage guidelines, or if it is deemed reasonably necessary by the site editor to protect the site editor's legal rights and/or property; or (vi) this site is purchased by a third party, in which case that third party will be able to use the information in the same manner as set forth in this policy. In the event you choose to use links displayed on this Website to visit other Websites, you are advised to read the privacy policies published on those sites. 

**Email.** Politics4All is very concerned about your privacy and we will never provide your email address to a third party without your explicit permission. Politics4all may send out e-mails with Politics4all-related news, products, offers, surveys or promotions. You may also receive notification e-mails from Politics4All, which inform you of actions (e.g. friend requests) that have been performed on the site. If you do not want to receive e-mail from us, please visit the Your Setting/Privacy section of your User Profile and change your settings. However, please note that in all cases you will continue to receive all system e-mails (e.g. those regarding forgotten user passwords) and/or legal notices (e.g. updates to our policies) from us. 

### Editing or deleting your account information

You are provided with the ability to edit the information stored for your user account information during registration, by editing your user profile. You can request that your user account be deleted; to do so, please contact us. Content or other information that you may have provided, and that is not stored within your user account, such as a group, may continue to remain on the site, even after your user account is deleted. Please see our Terms of Use for more information. 

### Changes to this privacy policy

Changes may be made to this policy from time to time. You will be notified of substantial changes to this policy either by through the posting of a prominent announcement on the site, and/or by a mail message sent to the e-mail address you have provided, which is stored within your user settings. 

### Conditions of Use

If you decide to visit Politics4All Website, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of Alabama State law. 

### Contact information

If you have any questions about this policy or about this Website, please feel free to contact us via email at privacy(at)politics4all(dot)com.
